http://www.affordablelighting.com/privacy-policy

Close
Please Login
If you have purchased with us online you can login to view your past orders, view your Quote Lists, or Manage Your Account and shipping/billing addresses.
Username
Password
Remember Me
Log in
Create an account
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
Customers can use the handy re-order button to place an order for the same items.
Products
Shop By CategoryHID LightingLED LightingLight & Pole KitsLight PolesAdapters & BullhornsShop By SolutionSports LightingParking Lot LightingEnergy SavingShop By TypeLEDMetal HalideAll Light Fixtures
Resources
Advanced Search What Kind of Lighting Do I need? Glossary Ball Field Lighting Catalog
Company Info
What We CarryWe Buy Surplus!About UsContact Us
Latest News
Privacy Policy
Affordable LiGHTING Terms of Service and Privacy Policy
1. Terms By accessing the web site at http://www.affordablelighting.com, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
2. Use License Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Affordable LiGHTING's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Affordable LiGHTING's web site;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Affordable LiGHTING at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer The materials on Affordable LiGHTING's web site are provided "as is". Affordable LiGHTING makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Affordable LiGHTING does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations In no event shall Affordable LiGHTING or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Affordable LiGHTING's Internet site, even if Affordable LiGHTING or a Affordable LiGHTING authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata The materials appearing on Affordable LiGHTING's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Affordable LiGHTING does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Affordable LiGHTING may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Affordable LiGHTING does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links Affordable LiGHTING has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Affordable LiGHTING of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications Affordable LiGHTING may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law Any claim relating to Affordable LiGHTING's web site shall be governed by the laws of Alabama without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us, and it is Affordable LiGHTING's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Affordable LiGHTING may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Affordable LiGHTING's sole discretion.
NOT EXACTLY SURE?....
If you’ve a list of items and are not exactly sure of what to order just send us your list and we’ll go over with you what products you’ll need in order to get the job done right!
Send Us Your List
